export const miscelaneous_1 = [
    {
        choices: ["II only", "I only", "II and IV", "I and IV"],
        correctAnswer: "I and IV",
        question: "Which of the following flow meters measure the average fluid velocity in a pipe rather than a point or local velocity?&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;I. venturi meter&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;II. pitot tube&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;III. impact tube&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;IV. orifice meter&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;V. hot wire anemometer",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["-sec x", "-sin x", "sec x", "csc x"],
        correctAnswer: "-sin x",
        question: "if y = cosx, what is dy/dx?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["8", "16", "2", "10"],
        correctAnswer: "10",
        question: "What is the radix of the binary number system?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["profitability", "monopoly", "competition", "inventory"],
        correctAnswer: "monopoly",
        question: "It occurs when a unique product or service is available only from a single supplier and entry of all other possible suppliers prevented:&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["1/2 sinxcosx", "-2sinxcosx", "2sinx/secx", "2 sinxcos(1/2x)"],
        correctAnswer: "2sinx/secx",
        question: "What is the equivalent expression for sin2x?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["mass", "radius", "number of protons", "number of neutrons"],
        correctAnswer: "number of protons",
        question: "The element tin has ten different stable isotopes. The atomic nuclei of all isotopes have the same:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["square statute mile", "square nautical mile", "square meter", "square foot"],
        correctAnswer: "square statute mile",
        question: "One section is equivalent to 1 _____.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["arc", "circle", "chord", "radius"],
        correctAnswer: "circle",
        question: "A plane closed curve, all points of which are the same distance from a point within, called the center is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Re = drag force/viccous forces", "Re = bouyant forces/inertial force", "Re = Inertial forces/viscous forces", "Re = viscous forces/inertial forces"],
        correctAnswer: "Re = Inertial forces/viscous forces",
        question: "Which of the following ratios is correct in providing a physical meaning for the Reynolds number, Re?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["d = sqrt. [(x1 - y1)^2 + (x2 - y2)^2] ", "d = sqrt. [(x1-x2)^2 - (y1-y2)^2]", "d = sqrt. [(x1^2 - x2^2) + (y1^2 - y2^2)]", "d = sqrt. [(x2 - x1)^2 + (y2 - y1)^2]"],
        correctAnswer: "d = sqrt. [(x2 - x1)^2 + (y2 - y1)^2]",
        question: "In finding the distance, d, between two points, which equation is the appropriate one to use?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["243", "81", "54", "729"],
        correctAnswer: "729",
        question: "The value of (3^3)^2 Is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["all of the above", "the fluid must be incompressible", "the fluid must be inviscid", "all points evaluated must be on the same streamline"],
        correctAnswer: "all of the above",
        question: "Under which of the following conditions is Bernoulli&amp;amp;#39;s equation valid?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["one trillion", "one billion", "one quadrillion", "one quintilillion"],
        correctAnswer: "one quadrillion",
        question: "The number 1 followed by 15 zeros is known as",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["clinometer", "flowmeter", "hydrometer", "hygrometer"],
        correctAnswer: "hydrometer",
        question: "An instrument for measuring specific density of fluids",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["salvage value", "fixed cost", "sunk cost", "resale value"],
        correctAnswer: "sunk cost",
        question: "The difference between the book value and the actual lower resale value is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["All its trigonometric functions negative", "A positive sine and cosine", "A negative cotangent and cosecant", "A negative secant and tangent"],
        correctAnswer: "All its trigonometric functions negative",
        question: "An angle between 90 degrees and 180 degrees has:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Capital recovery factor and sinking fund factor are reciprocals.", "Single payment compound amount factor and single payment present worth factor are reciprocals", "Sinking fund factor and uniform series compound amount factor are reciprocals", "Capital recovery factor equals sinking fund factor plus the interest rate."],
        correctAnswer: "Capital recovery factor and sinking fund factor are reciprocals.",
        question: "Which of the following relationships between compound interest factors is NOT correct?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Denary number system", "Denary number system", "Decimal number system", "All of the above"],
        correctAnswer: "All of the above",
        question: "A number system usinga a  value (or base) of 10",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["F(delta)T = MV^2", "FT = M(delta)V", "FT = MV", "F(delta)V = M(delta)T"],
        correctAnswer: "FT = M(delta)V",
        question: "A general principle in the motion of a body can be stated as follows (F = force, M=mass, V= velocity, delta = change, T = time)",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["a sinusoid", "a square wave", "a hyperbola", "a cycloid"],
        correctAnswer: "a sinusoid",
        question: "If the second derivative of the equation of a curve is proportional to the negative of the equation of the same curve, what is the curve?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["proportional to the displacement of the material acted upon by the force", "Inversely proportional to the force acting", "Inversely proportional to the material&amp;amp;#39;s yield strength", "inversely proportional to the strain"],
        correctAnswer: "proportional to the displacement of the material acted upon by the force",
        question: "The stress in an elastic material is:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["scalar", "moment", "tensor", "resultant"],
        correctAnswer: "resultant",
        question: "What is the name for a vector that represents the sum of two vectors?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Septenary number system", "Sexagesimal number system", "Sexadecimai number system", "Senary number system"],
        correctAnswer: "Sexagesimal number system",
        question: "A number system using a place value (or base) of 60.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["scruple", "stere", "span", "section"],
        correctAnswer: "stere",
        question: "1 cubic meter is equivalent to 1 ______",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["1,000", "100", "1,000,000", "100,000"],
        correctAnswer: "100,000",
        question: "In Roman numerals, the doorframe written with the letter indicates that the number equivalent to the letter is to be multiplied by",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["3/4 H from the vertex", "2/3 from the vertex", "2/3 H from the vertex", "1/3 H from the vertex"],
        correctAnswer: "2/3 H from the vertex",
        question: "The center of gravity of an isosceles triangle whose height H is on the median line",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["single payment compound amount factor", "sinking fund factor", "capital recovery factor", "single payment present worth factor"],
        correctAnswer: "single payment present worth factor",
        question: "In the formula P=F(1+i)^-n the factor (1+i)^-n is called the",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["central tendency", "a normal distance", "dispersion", "a standard distance"],
        correctAnswer: "dispersion",
        question: "In statistics, the standard deviation measures:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["I, II, and III", "I and II", "IV only", "I only"],
        correctAnswer: "I, II, and III",
        question: "Which of the following properties are intensitive properties?&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;I. temperature&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;II. pressure&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;III. composition&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;IV. mass",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["strictly nonzero", "always numerical", "defined only over a finite", "always continous"],
        correctAnswer: "always numerical",
        question: "How can the values of a random variable defined over a sample space be described?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["510,000 Ghz", "589,000 Ghz", "295,000 Ghz", "1,020,000 Ghz"],
        correctAnswer: "510,000 Ghz",
        question: "Frequency f of monochromatic yellow light which as a wavelenth (gamma) of 589 nm (nanometers) in vacuum is nearest to:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["150 million km", "100 million km", "125 million km", "175 million km"],
        correctAnswer: "100 million km",
        question: "An astronomical unit is approximately equal to",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["if he graduated with a BSME degree and has a 4 years of practice as a RME", "none of these", "he has 4 years practice as a MPE", "if he has a BSME degree, passed the examinations for RME and has 4 years practice as RME"],
        correctAnswer: "he has 4 years practice as a MPE",
        question: "Mechanical Plant Engineer (MPE) may be allowed to take the licensure examination for PME if",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["764", "746", "674", "476"],
        correctAnswer: "746",
        question: "1 horsepower is equivalent to how many Watts?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["6.67 x 10^-9", "6.67 x 10^-11", "6.67 x 10^-12", "6.67 x 10^-10"],
        correctAnswer: "6.67 x 10^-10",
        question: "The gravitational constant G is equivalent to ______ N.m^2/kg^2",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["1243", "54", "312", "12433"],
        correctAnswer: "54",
        question: "The nearest whole number to the value of 2/3 (700)^2/3 is:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["1 PME, 1 RME, and 1 CPM", "1 RME is charge of every shift", "1 RME, 2 CPM", "1 PME, 2 RME"],
        correctAnswer: "1 RME, 2 CPM",
        question: "To comply with the requirements of the Mechanical Engineering Law on the minimum complement of mechanical engineers, a mechanical plant with a combine prime movers rating of 373 KW must have in its employ the following:&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;(NOTE: the plant is operating in 3 shifts)",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["parabola", "hyperbola", "ellipse", "circle"],
        correctAnswer: "hyperbola",
        question: "If a right circular cone is cut parallel with the axis of symmetry, you would reveal:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["The probability of an event is always positive and less than or equal to one.", "If events E, and E2 are mutually exclusive, then P(E1+E2) = P(E1) + P(E2) - P(E1E2).", "If Eo is an event which cannot occur in the sample space, the probability of Eo is zero", "If events E, and Eo are mutually exclusive, then the probability of both events occuring is zero."],
        correctAnswer: "If events E, and E2 are mutually exclusive, then P(E1+E2) = P(E1) + P(E2) - P(E1E2).",
        question: "Which of the following probability is not valid?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["a helix", "a hypocycloid", "a cycloid", "an epicycloid"],
        correctAnswer: "a helix",
        question: "What type of curve is generated by a point which moves in uniform circular motion about an axis, while travelling with a constant speed, v, parallel to the axis?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["100,000", "10,000", "100", "1,000"],
        correctAnswer: "100",
        question: "In Roman numerals, the bar written above the letter indicates that number equivalent to the letter is to be multiplied by ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["0 degrees F", "0 degrees C", "0 Kelvin", "0 Rankine"],
        correctAnswer: "0 Kelvin",
        question: "Absolute zero is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["a sample space", "an event", "a random point", "a finite set"],
        correctAnswer: "an event",
        question: "What is a possible outcome of an experiment called?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["6.2 meters", "305 cm", "5 ft", "240 inches"],
        correctAnswer: "240 inches",
        question: "Point &amp;amp;quot;A&amp;amp;quot; in an irregular shaped rotating body is 10 ft. from an instantaneous axis. At the same Instant a point &amp;amp;quot;B&amp;amp;quot; in the body is to have twice the velocity",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Velocity of sound in solids may be calculated from their elastic modulus and density", "Velocity of sound in gases is independent of pressure.", "Sound is propagated by longitudinal compressional waves.", "Sound waves do not exhibit refraction in passing between media"],
        correctAnswer: "Sound waves do not exhibit refraction in passing between media",
        question: "All of the following statements about sound are correct, EXCEPT:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Sexagesimal number system", "Bidecimal number system", "Vigesimal number system", "Duodecimal number system"],
        correctAnswer: "Vigesimal number system",
        question: "A number system using a plane value of base of 20",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["1,500 radians", "1.57 rad", "3,142 rad", "1,000 rad"],
        correctAnswer: "1.57 rad",
        question: "Ninety degrees is equal to ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["chilliagon", "milliagon", "centillion", "google"],
        correctAnswer: "google",
        question: "The number 1 followed by 100 zeros or 10^100 is called",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Cost of producing a product or rendering a service.", "A series of equal payments occuring at equal periods of time.", "Earned interest due at the end of each interest period.", "Total annual overhead assigned to a unit of production."],
        correctAnswer: "A series of equal payments occuring at equal periods of time.",
        question: "An &amp;amp;quot;annuity&amp;amp;quot; is defined as",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["It is an approximate solution.", "It permits one to calculate the skin friction on a flat plate.", "It is valid for laminar flow.", "It is valid only for potential flow."],
        correctAnswer: "It is valid only for potential flow.",
        question: "Which of the following is not true regarding the Biasius boundary layer solution?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["median", "hypotenuse", "quadrilateral", "apothem"],
        correctAnswer: "hypotenuse",
        question: "The side oppossite the right angle of a right triangle",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["theorem", "postulate", "axiom ", "corollary"],
        correctAnswer: "theorem",
        question: "The volume of a circular cylinder is equal to the product of its base and altitude",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["1.0", "pi^2", "pi", "1/pi"],
        correctAnswer: "pi",
        question: "Circular pitch times diametral pitch equals",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Vigesimal number system ", "Duodecimal number system", "Octal number system", "Hexadecimal number"],
        correctAnswer: "Hexadecimal number",
        question: "A number system which needs sixteen symbols, the 10 numerals and the letters A, B, C, D, E and F is called",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["equal to the weight of the fluid displaced", "proportional to the weight of the body", "proportional to the depth of submergence", "independent of the specific gravity of the liquid"],
        correctAnswer: "equal to the weight of the fluid displaced",
        question: "The loss of the weight of the body submerged in a fluid is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["astronomical unit", "steradian", "astronomical orbit", "lightyear"],
        correctAnswer: "astronomical unit",
        question: "The radius of the Earth&amp;amp;#39;s orbit around the Sun (the average distance between the Sun and Earth) is known as",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["stere", "section", "quintal", "ton"],
        correctAnswer: "quintal",
        question: "100 kilograms is equivalent to 1",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Air is more humid on rainy days.", "Boiling frees water of gases.", "Soda pop is bottled under pressure.", "Air bubbles from on the sides of a warm glass of water."],
        correctAnswer: "Air is more humid on rainy days.",
        question: "Which of the following does not illustrate the effect of temperature or pressure on gas solubility?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["oK/a", "hK/a", "ha/K", "aK/h"],
        correctAnswer: "hK/a",
        question: "If the sine of angle A is given as K, what would be the tangent of angle A?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["1,2,3,4,5,...", "0,2,4,6,8,...", "1/2,3/2,5/2,7/2,...", "1,3,5,9,..."],
        correctAnswer: "0,2,4,6,8,...",
        question: "The series expansion for cos x contains which powers of x?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["hyperbola", "circle", "straight line", "parabola"],
        correctAnswer: "straight line",
        question: "If the first derivative of the equation of a curve is a constant, the curve is a:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["They are mutually exclusive.", "They are not identically distributed.", "(A) or (B)", "They are uncorrelated."],
        correctAnswer: "They are uncorrelated.",
        question: "If two random variables are independently distributed, what is the relationship?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["1.013 x 10^5 Pa", "1000 kg/cm^2", "1.013 bar", "14.7 bar"],
        correctAnswer: "1000 kg/cm^2",
        question: "Which is not equivalent to 1 atm?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["acceleration", "displacement", "velocity", "speed"],
        correctAnswer: "speed",
        question: "Which of the following is not a vector quantity?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["The number is divisible is divisible by 5 If it ends with 5 or 0.", "The number is divisible by 9 if the sum of its digits is divisible by 9", "The number is divisible by 12 If it is divisible by 4 and 3", "The number is divisible by 4 if the number formed by the last 2 digits by the last 2 digits is divisible by 3"],
        correctAnswer: "The number is divisible by 4 if the number formed by the last 2 digits by the last 2 digits is divisible by 3",
        question: "Indicate the false statement about rules of divisibility",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["may act as either a base or an acid in chemical reactions", "has been craed by bombardment with high energy protons", "reacts violently with water", "has a valence of -2"],
        correctAnswer: "may act as either a base or an acid in chemical reactions",
        question: "An amphoteric hydroxide is one which:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["the maximum moment occurs at the reaction", "the moment diagram is a straight line", "the shear at the reaction is a minimum", "the shear at the center of the beam is zero"],
        correctAnswer: "the shear at the center of the beam is zero",
        question: "For a simple beam supported at each end and which is uniformly loaded",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Photon energy varies with source intensity, i.e. a bright light source emits photons of higher energy than a dim source.", "Photons are small quanta of electromagnetic energy", "Velocity of photons in vacuum is c, the speed of light, 3x10^10 cm/sec", "Energy of photons varies according to E = hf, where h is Planck&amp;amp;#39;s"],
        correctAnswer: "Velocity of photons in vacuum is c, the speed of light, 3x10^10 cm/sec",
        question: "All of the following statements about photons are correct, EXCEPT:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["P(1+r/m)^n/m", "P(1+r/m)^r", "P(1+r/m)^m", "none of these"],
        correctAnswer: "none of these",
        question: "A principal sum P is invested at a nominal interest rate r, compounded m times a year, for n years. The accumulated amount at the end of this period will be",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["I and II", "I and IV", "I, III, and IV", "I, II, III, and IV"],
        correctAnswer: "I, II, III, and IV",
        question: "Under certain flow conditions, the expression for the first law of thermodynamics for a control volume reduces to Bernoulli&amp;amp;#39;s equation:&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;gz1+v1^2/2+P1/p = gz2+v2^2/2+P2/p&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;Which combination of the following conditions is necessary and sufficient to reduce the first law for a control volume to Bernoulli&amp;amp;#39;s equation?&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;I. steady flow&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;II. incompressible&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;III. no frictional losses of energy&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;IV. no heat transfer or change in internal energy",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Electrons of highest energy are located in the outer orbitals.", "Each shell may contain up to n^2 orbitals, but not exceeding", "Eacth orbital can contain one electron.", "K, L, M, etc. shells are designation representing the principal quantum number n = 1,2,3 etc."],
        correctAnswer: "Eacth orbital can contain one electron.",
        question: "All of the following statements about the electron structure of atome are correct, EXCEPT:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Bernoulli&amp;amp;#39;s equation only holds on the same streamline.", "steady flows do not change with time at any point.", "The Navier-Stroke equation is the equation of motion for a viscous Newtonian fluid.", "The Reynolds number is the ration of the viscous force to the inertial force."],
        correctAnswer: "Bernoulli&amp;amp;#39;s equation only holds on the same streamline.",
        question: "Which of the following statements is incorrect?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Decimal number system", "Duodecimal number decimal", "Bidecimal number system", "Vigesimal number system"],
        correctAnswer: "Duodecimal number decimal",
        question: "The terms &amp;amp;quot;dozen&amp;amp;quot; and &amp;amp;quot;gross&amp;amp;quot; used what number system?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Electic field maxima and minima occur out of phase with those of the associated magnetic field.", "Directions of the electric field, of the magnetic field, and of propagation are mutually perpendicular.", "Field intensity changes take place, but no displacement of mass occurs in the path of electromagnetic waves", "Electromagnetic wave are transverse waves that consist of mutually coupled, changing electric and magnetic fields."],
        correctAnswer: "Electic field maxima and minima occur out of phase with those of the associated magnetic field.",
        question: "All of the statements about electromagnetic waves are correct, EXCEPT:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["at the lower bound of x", "(A) or (B) or (C)", "at the upper bound of x", "strictly between the upper and the lower bounds of x"],
        correctAnswer: "(A) or (B) or (C)",
        question: "Consider a strictly convex function of one variable, x, with a lower bound and upper bound on x. For what value(s) of x will the function be minimized?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["32.2 ft^2/sec", "980 ft/sec", "64.34 ft/sec^2", "35.30 km/hr/sec"],
        correctAnswer: "35.30 km/hr/sec",
        question: "The standard acceleration due to gravity, g is equal to:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Fourth power", "First power", "Third power", "Second power"],
        correctAnswer: "Fourth power",
        question: "The moment of inertia of any plane figure can be expressed in units of length to the:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["none of the above", "lbm/ft-sec^2", "m/s", "ft^2/sec"],
        correctAnswer: "none of the above",
        question: "What are the units of Reynolds number for pipe flow?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["0.10", "0.064", "0.08", "0.008"],
        correctAnswer: "0.064",
        question: "What is the friction factor for fully developed flow in a circular pipe where Reynolds number is 1000?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["F = MLT", "F = MLT^2", "F = ML^-1 T^-2", "F = MT^2L^-1"],
        correctAnswer: "F = MLT^2",
        question: "In mechanics, if mass (M), length (L), and time (T) are selected as primary units, force (F) will have the following equation",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["U = Q - W", "Tds = dH - Vdp", "Tds = dU - pdV", "H = U - pV"],
        correctAnswer: "H = U - pV",
        question: "Which of the following thermodynamic relations is incorrect?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["phase angle", "sum", "magnitude", "resultant"],
        correctAnswer: "resultant",
        question: "The vector which represents the sum of a group of force vectors is called the:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["depreciation", "taxes", "interest", "supplies"],
        correctAnswer: "taxes",
        question: "The following type item, which is common to both the fixed and operating cost of an enterprise is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["efficiency", "bond", "rate of return", "annuity"],
        correctAnswer: "efficiency",
        question: "Output over input",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["proportion factor", "theorem", "valuation", "power"],
        correctAnswer: "proportion factor",
        question: "A statement of equality between two ratios:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["1 lumen", "pi lumens", "2 lumens", "4 pi lumens"],
        correctAnswer: "4 pi lumens",
        question: "A one candle power light source radiates luminous flux at the rate of",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["unsupported length to its least radius of gyration", "length to its moment of Inertia", "length to its minimum width", "unsupported length to its maximum radius of gyration"],
        correctAnswer: "unsupported length to its least radius of gyration",
        question: "The &amp;amp;quot;SLENDERNESS RATIO&amp;amp;quot; of a column is generally defined as the ratio its:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["5 dozens", "144 pieces", "10 dozens", "100 pieces"],
        correctAnswer: "100 pieces",
        question: "1 gross is equivalent to",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["1/8", "3/4", "1/2", "1/4"],
        correctAnswer: "1/2",
        question: "For fully developed laminar flow of fluids through pipes, the average velocity is what fraction of the maximum velocity in the pipe?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["corollary", "postulate", "theorem", "axiom"],
        correctAnswer: "theorem",
        question: "Two triangles are congruent if two angles and the included side of one are equal respectively to two angles and the included side of the other",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Capital recovery with a return.", "Straight line depreciation plus interest on first cost.", "Straight line depreciation plus average interest.", "Sinking fund depreciation plus interest on first cost"],
        correctAnswer: "Straight line depreciation plus average interest.",
        question: "In determining the average annual cost of a project, the formula P-S/n + (P-S)(i/2)(n+1/n) + Si represents the economic method of",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["5", "2", "3", "4"],
        correctAnswer: "3",
        question: "One foot is equivalent to how many hands?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Octonumerals", "Octonary number system", "Octonumber system", "Octenary number system"],
        correctAnswer: "Octenary number system",
        question: "What is another name of octal number system?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["increases the ductility", "increases the hardness", "increases the resistance to shock", "decreases the resistance to fatigue"],
        correctAnswer: "increases the hardness",
        question: "The use of carbon in steel",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["A = P(1+i)^-n", "A = F [(1+i)^n/i]", "A = F [(1+i)^n-1/i(1+i)^n]", "A = F [i/(1+i)^n-1]"],
        correctAnswer: "A = F [i/(1+i)^n-1]",
        question: "A fund established to produced a desired amount at the end or a given period by means of series of payments throughout the period is called a sinking fund, and is represented by the formula:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["The values of all functions repeat themselves every 45 degrees", "All functions are units of length or angular measure.", "The graphs of all functions are continuous.", "All functions are dimensionless units"],
        correctAnswer: "All functions are dimensionless units",
        question: "The following is a characteristic of all trigonometric functions:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Brownian movement", "hydration", "oxidation", "plastic flow"],
        correctAnswer: "hydration",
        question: "The chemical process which occurs when water is added to cement is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["a kg m/s^2", "a rate of change of energy", "a unit of power", "a Newton meter"],
        correctAnswer: "a Newton meter",
        question: "Which of the following is the definition of the Joule?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Radix", "Logarithm", "Cologarithm", "Index"],
        correctAnswer: "Radix",
        question: "The base number of the number system",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["hecto", "Deci", "Tera", "atto"],
        correctAnswer: "hecto",
        question: "If deka means 10^1 and kilo means 10^3, then 10^2 is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["faRe", "f a 64/Re", "f a 1/Re", "faRe^2"],
        correctAnswer: "f a 64/Re",
        question: "For pipe flow in laminar flow region, how is the friction factor related to the Reynolds number?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["30,000,000 m/s", "3 x 10^6 km/s", "3 x 10^4 km/s", "3 x 10^5 km/s"],
        correctAnswer: "3 x 10^5 km/s",
        question: "The speed of light is nearly",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["experimental results for inviscid fluids", "experimental results for viscous fluids", "applying the principle of conservation of mass", "calculations based on potential flow"],
        correctAnswer: "experimental results for viscous fluids",
        question: "Where does the Moody diagram for friction factors for pipe flow come from?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["1.603 x 10^-19", "1.602 x 10^-12", "1.602 x 10^-16", "1.602 x 10^-14"],
        correctAnswer: "1.602 x 10^-14",
        question: "1 electron volt is equivalent to how many Joules?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["133.3", "100.0", "200.0", "166.7"],
        correctAnswer: "100.0",
        question: "The pressure of 1 torr is equivalent to how many Pascals?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["directly proportional to its radius", "directly proportional to its length", "independent of its length", "independent of its radius"],
        correctAnswer: "directly proportional to its length",
        question: "The mass moment of Inertia of a cylinder about its central axis perpendicular to a circular cross section is:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["1054", "1064", "1045", "1036"],
        correctAnswer: "1036",
        question: "1 Btu is equivalent to how many Joules?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["load factor", "demand factor", "power factor", "Capacity factor"],
        correctAnswer: "Capacity factor",
        question: "The ratio between the average load and total available capacity",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["120", "720", "60", "360"],
        correctAnswer: "60",
        question: "The number of board feet in a plank 3 inches thick, 1 foot wide and 20 foot length is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["a maximum", "zero", "equal to unity", "Indeterminate"],
        correctAnswer: "zero",
        question: "For a system to be in equilibrium, the sum of the external forces acting on the system must be:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Energy of a wave with the square of its amplitude.", "Diffraction, or bending of a wave, occurs around the edges of obstacles.", "Interference is interaction of waves. The observed effect is based on the principle of superposition.", "Wave frequency changes on entering a medium where the velocity of propagation is changed."],
        correctAnswer: "Wave frequency changes on entering a medium where the velocity of propagation is changed.",
        question: "All of the following are characteristic of waves, EXCEPT:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["0", "2", "3", "1"],
        correctAnswer: "2",
        question: "How many independent properties are required to completely fix the equilibrium state of a pure gaseous compound?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["projectile energy", "a cosine expansion series", "projectile motion", "a straight line"],
        correctAnswer: "a straight line",
        question: "The equation y = a1 + a2x is an algebraic expression for which the following choices?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["centigoogle", "googleplex", "myriad", "milligoogle"],
        correctAnswer: "googleplex",
        question: "The speed of 10 exponen google or 10^google is called",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["a cummutative distributive", "a set of random events", "a fuzzy set", "a sample space"],
        correctAnswer: "a sample space",
        question: "In probability theory, what is the set of all possible outcomes of an experiment called?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["400", "20", "40", "power"],
        correctAnswer: "40",
        question: "The number of the board feet in a plank 2 inches thick, one foot wide and 20 feet long is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Canada", "Japan", "America", "none of these"],
        correctAnswer: "none of these",
        question: "The only country that recongnizes the mechanical engineering licensure of Filipinos issued by the Professional Regulation Commission and allowed to used the practice as RME",
        topic: "NA"
    },
]